there has been multiple suhara related
catastrophes going on the first one is
this the concrete maker that is Scalla
mumbo put together and the one that I've
been stocking and using that's that's
hashtag teamwork for you in the
architects yeah well you know I've been
using it and I've got some concrete that
I've been making and I was you know just
making some some white concrete here and
there and all of a sudden they exploded
and it's all gone it's it's it
disappeared I honestly don't know what I
did wrong I'll be honest with you I
think maybe I accidentally unloaded it I
was just you know I was just using it
and it um it um blew up and there's one
thing that Mambo said to me he said hey
Graham
don't break it I'm in a little bit of
trouble I'm in a little bit a lot of
trouble
so um you know I could just try and
remake this just you know make I know
some redstone I got so I got some
redstone stuff here there was a slime
block somewhere in there there was a
there was a couple of Pistons going
round redstone torches and such the like
of course we're all real dragon Bros
here so a real bro would remake a Bros
concrete maker but some bros some bros
don't know how to make concrete makers
and I'm one of those pros so we're just
gonna we're just gonna do our best shall
we something sous went something like
this I'm sure I'm sure of it and then
went down like this
yeah there's anyone I don't have a clue
so I'm doing my best
it definitely had a slime block or two
when in doubt just to make it look super
complicated that's that's just what
redstone is do all they do is they just
make stuff look super complicated but
it's actually really easy just to
confuse the rest of us so we'll just you
know could dispense some carrots I guess
and what else can we we can add what
else looks impressive Wales looks quite
impressive on this oh yeah it was
definitely linked up at some point over
here so we can we can do something here
hoppers look quite impressive maybe if
we put a couple of hoppers there put an
item in it
there we go that that looks impressive I
mean doesn't go anywhere I'm running out
of things that we can do for this
I don't really know it looks roughly the
same as it did now I'm learning the
glass doesn't treat redstone very well I
have no idea if we put a couple more
slime blocks that looks like a thing
blimey
I have no idea what I'm doing yeah you
know what that looks good I think all we
need now is a minecart and we're good to
go yep there we go yeah that looks that
looks similar right
okay well job done all we got to do now
is just leave a little note explaining
what's happened left a quick sign saying
hi mumbo and slight accident but because
I'm a bro I fixed it up for you best I
could dragon bro okay that's the best I
can do yeah that's that's pretty much
how it will work some pretty sure that's
how it will went down it was something
like that and if mumbo could fix this
for me as soon as possible I'd be I'd be
really really grateful really really
grateful as I was saying though that's
not the only Sahara related disaster
that has occurred since episode 100 and
101 and I'm I'm not actually able to
finish these over there until I get this
concrete maker fixed anyway the disaster
that has occurred
is this idea the subordinate planned
that are selling stuff have made a giant
thing outside of Sahara taunting us and
look what it says shop at idea we have
stock now there's only one thing that
that can mean which is they've bought
everything so I'm not gonna be surprised
if I open this up yep there's absolutely
nothing in here but that also means they
must have spent a huge amount of
diamonds now I actually don't know how
where the now I actually don't know
where the Diamonds go in Sahara somehow
they just magically end up in the vault
I think your Scout takes care of it but
look at this look how many diamonds this
is I can't be like 9 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8
there's well over like 150 diamonds here
so what if we just get the architects
together and stock this up so much that
we run them out of business because they
can't they cannot surely they can not
surely keep buying from Sahara forever
I just great isn't it it's great we've
got customers but there is an issue that
Sahara is actually no longer working so
we're gonna have to call in the
maintenance crew and get them in here
because something's gone wrong with the
system it got overloaded or something so
what we're gonna do well we're gonna
have to burn this to the ground actually
at some point but we're gonna have to
stock Sahara but I have to wait for
everyone to get together which is soon
because speaking of the dragon Bros we
need to get ourselves another member and
I think I know just who and just how to
do it but first we're gonna have to get
ourselves another dragon head which
means going into the end portal and I'm
pretty sure that almost every single
nether portal has been absolutely rigged
to blow up
single-point so we're gonna take a load
of precautions with us I've got my total
ban of undying okay we're good okay
we're good
this one also might be might be rigged
if I got like a shield or something
no no shields no shields okay well I've
got my totem of undying I've got fire
resistance and regen on let's go for it
that wasn't there before it looks like
we're all good
that was that was seriously close I
thought it was gonna go I'm pretty sure
people have been rigging all of this
stuff anyway so what we need to do is
fly off into the distance and get
ourselves another dragon head for the
next contestant that is going to be a
dragon Road well we got to do now is
find ourselves a temple somewhere in at
the end which is sometimes easier said
than done it's a bit of pot luck to be
honest with you
okay so I've just found somewhere
completely covered in water that's not
unusual I've been searching for like
five minutes and I can't find a single
end temple ah finally we found one and
hopefully there's a boat there is a boat
and there's a dragon heard it only took
a very very long time
and we head back I thought that was
gonna be a quick job but I couldn't find
it now I have to get out somehow I need
to get out of here aha a way out at last
I took a big risk looking at this
alright we got a couple of ender pearls
isn't that how you get out am I just
stuck here forever
no come on why doesn't that work oh
there we go huh I could have sworn it
wasn't working okay and now we go back
yeah we did it we're back we got the
dragon head now all we need to do is in
chant this and we are good to go we are
ready to go we've got the dragon head
but before we do I've got to stop off at
Sahara and say oh my goodness thank you
so much to everyone that went on the
store and literally IRL shopped at
Sahara and I've got to say because of
that we actually got quite a lot of
comments saying it's not the Sahara logo
without the Bombo because our original
design on the t-shirts it doesn't have
the moustache in the Hat so for a
limited time only
we'll end December 4th we are doing a
t-shirt with the full logo with the
mustache and the hat but that isn't even
all here's a picture of me wearing the
the new bumbo exclusive so this is like
a limited edition one but that isn't it
because if you add the coupon sake in
capital letters then you get a free pair
of socks with every order over 15 pounds
which you know who doesn't like free
socks so check out the link in the
description it will take you to the
architect store where you can get a
literal shop at Sahara t-shirt and you
can get some free socks so I mean that's
insane anyway now that we have got our
dragon head it is time to go and meet up
with mumbo and actually you know explain
what the whole dragon bro thing is about
he doesn't actually know he doesn't
actually know I do have some questions
all right
I have some questions guys okay what's
all this then what is all this I
understand how anyone could build a
bumpy road you're gonna have to explain
to me what that is all about because I
can't have a notice that my head has
quadrupled in size alright okay because
I came a I can't I can't believe that
you guys broke into my bunker I know my
password security wasn't exactly
fantastic I'm still 1 2 3 to come over
to my bunker and start jamming codes in
that you know that I would program we
didn't have to upset that you managed to
break in okay I can't believe that I'm
now stuck with this I'm not upset
because now you are a dragon bro a
scouser dragon bro I'm a dragon bro
b-dubs is a dragon bro and basically
what we do is we bro you know you have
we bro dude we bro as long as you do
something that's like dragon bro then
that's okay okay bro what about this
but this P bro and thready some phone
don't pick out no this is bro
this is more bro table spread this is
bro oh that was dragon bro you know I
mean yeah that was totally dragon bro I
mean he still lost me I mean I I feel
like I'm gonna be doing unintentional
bro things for a while so if I do do
something bro you can tell me that it's
bro maybe for a little bit
you'll get it it's fine basically
everything you do is either bro or not
bro we I guess dragon bros keep our
brazen line yeah all right we just bro
bro okay dude that's bro
that's bro yeah that's bro that's bro
that's awesome
Oh Oh looking up like that yeah yeah
he's gonna be a good dragon bro great
I'll pick this up alright I'll pick this
up so you ain't a real dragon bro until
you've brode someone else yeah we've all
brought someone I brought green eyebrows
yeah me and then we both together broad
no wait bro peanuts you're on your own
bro yes
so you guys alright okay so yeah I've
you haven't brought any more well I've
only been a bro for like three minutes
so I think that still still a brawl time
okay alright there's a few people online
we could there's yeah you just pick one
people that you have to be alive into my
so X and cover our forces online we
could go for the closest you don't have
to do want to be a bro okay yeah we can
bro false all right okay um do you have
do you have bro headgear there we go
track dragon bro bro bro
drop wait we should show in the dragon
bro base yes yes so what do I have to do
here cuz otherwise I will die the
architect bunker key we put that in you
wait for the begin and then you dragon
burn both cough both cough dragon bro
if you don't do that mumble there is a
it's a sure death
I made this by the way agree and have
you seen this I have I have been inside
this is this is dragon dragon bro
meeting dragon bro headquarters oh my
word there's piston door action going on
right okay so this is the squad this is
the squad squad standing on your own
head is that bro
that's bro that's very bro I love it's
not bro well there's someone missing
here b-dubs
oh yeah not turning up to a meeting that
ain't bro dude no man ain't bro that
ain't breathing dragon bro debrief time
we're gonna go after false I actually
have a little plan so let me take you
through it cuz we're actually gonna need
this is actually gonna take a little bit
of like finesse on our part and really
work together as dragon bros okay we've
got by the bucketloads gonna have to do
this is gonna be a little bit
complicated so we're gonna put outside
the front of her base a big old sign
with a pumpkin on it and we're gonna
have a mode of red-herring signs so this
is gonna be like a blah blah blah blah
blah blah on the signs right correct I'm
what we're gonna do is I'm gonna have a
dispenser this girl's gonna have the
dragon head and mumbo is gonna have the
lever because he's the one that's got
got to dispense yeah okay and I've got
the redstone skills exactly so what
we're gonna do is we're going to create
this it's gonna have loads of like just
words on it so false we'll be reading it
she'll be like looking looking looking
looking at this time we sneak up behind
her decidin tell her to put the pumpkin
on her head
- like reveal a secret message or
something is total nonsense
but either way she should take off her
helmet for that split second to put on
the pumpkin that's when we sneak up
behind her we put the dispenser down put
the dragon head in and activate it
that's why we need all three of us so
it's that split second okay we gotta you
realize I press shift with my thumb dude
remove actually that that's the anti bra
move I'm gonna pretend to be false right
yeah and when we countdown do we say
three two one broke and then we perform
the dragon head chant which is humming
and then we leave is there an option to
leave the room oh this is you can leave
this room when you can take that dragon
head off of your head yes now you're a
life dude right that's now that's bro oh
your life slogan boom okay I'm gonna
pretend to be false okay so I'm gonna
dice down my might Spencer ahead of time
additional visibility potion should we
just go and do it should we just go and
set this up but should we just give it a
go yeah let's go do it let's give it a
go everyone's got the plan down all
right we need to think this through a
little bit we need to put the signs
somewhere where she's gonna find them
without her seeing us do it as well
goodness me yeah okay I didn't think
this all the way through this was a
pretty popular place and she doesn't
look like she's here inside the next to
the clock tower next to the clock tower
then you dive straight down the middle
okay this is perfect guys because then
we can hide behind these and then sneak
round well yeah that is how good we're
gonna be standing here for like five
days these days they're gonna come I
don't want to stress anyone else but
there's a green head chicken over there
I had noticed that chicken shrine that's
bro yeah that's bro could we ask her
should we say how about this cuz she's
on the server we could just say faulty
chickens escaped and then she might
this direction see what happens okay I'm
just I need to write a load of rubbish
on signs I mean rubbish basically just
repeating the same thing over and over
again yeah yeah she's gonna do she's
gonna see this she's gonna start reading
it and then okay okay and then she's
gonna punch the pumpkin off then she'll
take off the helmet and that's when we
stripe so we need we need to time this
incredibly quickly you'll have to place
it there exactly now if we come in from
this side if we come in from this side I
can place it here boom yeah that's all I
was saying all right
I said now we just wait now we just have
to wait how we wait now we wait did
anyone bring did anyone bring snacks no
I didn't bring snacks no what's this
invisibility Porsche gonna do agrees it
will be entertaining and it doesn't make
us look a little bit it means at least
our user names won't be visible look
don't take yours dude you've gone the
least invisible thing ever you literally
just shorts Yoshi stop this is the worst
thing we ever know this is me not bro
this is not a roast steak I can see
through your pants a skirt I can see
through everyone's pants is a real
problem I don't want to go out there it
smells badly in this corner as far don't
[Laughter]
if I turn around I feel like my nose
okay I'm running I'm running just been
very confused as to why there was
dispenser there and then and then and
then and we are the worst
[Laughter]
[Applause]
that was the Mickey Mouse operation I've
ever seen in my life well that was
probably the most messy
thing we've ever done we were waiting in
falses space for about 20 minutes and we
were debating several times whether she
was actually going to turn up or not but
it somehow somehow it worked out so you
know I'm just gonna take it so next
episode we're gonna have to get false
involved in the new Dragon done we're
gonna have to give her a tour of
everything the dragon bro team is kind
of growing and we still have no agenda
whatsoever brilliant it's absolutely
brilliant so that is all I have time for
in today's episode I did actually mean
to finish off making these but the
concrete maker broke so until mumbo
fixes this I'm probably gonna have to
hold off but it won't be long until I
can replicate this one to over and then
it will be done anyway thank you very
much for watching and if you're still
watching now I mean thank you thank you
very much but also check out the link in
the description because there are the
exclusive t-shirts and it is only a
limited time so make sure you check it
out thank you very much for watching and
good bye